<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<!--
  ~ Copyright 2018 Google LLC
  ~
  ~ Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
  ~ you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
  ~ You may obtain a copy of the License at
  ~
  ~     https://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
  ~
  ~ Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
  ~ distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
  ~ WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
  ~ See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
  ~ limitations under the License.
  -->

<resources>

  <!--
    LOI DATA FORMS
  -->

  <!-- Shown below fields that are required but left empty (TBD). -->
  <string name="required_task">This field is required</string>

  <!--
    LOCATION (GPS/CELL/WIFI) UPDATE ERROR MESSAGES
  -->

  <!-- Shown when user has refused to grant app fine grained location permission. -->
  <string name="no_fine_location_permissions">Cannot show current location without
    permission</string>
  <!-- Shown when an unknown error occurs obtaining fine grained location permission. -->
  <string name="location_updates_unknown_error">Failed to enable location updates</string>
  <!-- Shown when user has refused to enable location services in settings.-->
  <string name="location_disabled_in_settings">Please enable location in system settings</string>

  <string name="map_view">Map view</string>
  <string name="unexpected_error">An unexpected error has occurred</string>
  <string name="google_api_install_failed">Google Play Services installation failed</string>
  <string name="sign_out">Sign out</string>
  <string name="ok">OK</string>
  <string name="collect_data">Collect data</string>

  <!-- Untranslated strings -->
  <string name="offline_area_selector">Select area to download</string>
  <string name="offline_area_selector_prompt">Select a base map for offline use</string>
  <string name="offline_area_selector_download">Download</string>
  <string name="camera">Camera</string>
  <string name="photo_preview">Preview</string>
  <string name="settings">Settings</string>
  <string name="offline_area_viewer_title">Downloaded area</string>
  <string name="offline_area_viewer_remove_button">Remove from device</string>
  <!-- Label of button used enter the offline area selector. -->
  <string name="offline_area_selector_select">Select area</string>
  <string name="no_basemaps_downloaded">No imagery downloaded for offline use. Tap “Select and download” to get started.</string>
  <string name="signing_in">Signing in</string>
  <!-- Precedes the build number shown in the side menu of debug builds. -->
  <string name="build">Build %s</string>

  <string name="tos_title">Terms of service</string>
  <string name="agree_terms">Agree</string>
  <string name="agree_checkbox">I agree</string>
  <string name="date">Date</string>
  <string name="time">Time</string>
  <!-- Other strings (to be organized) -->
  <string name="sync_status">Data sync status</string>

  <string name="add_point">Add point</string>
  <string name="complete_polygon">Complete</string>
  <string name="add_polygon_instructions">Drag the map and tap “Add point“ to add points to your polygon. To finish, return to the original point and tap “Complete“.</string>

  <string name="road_map">Road map</string>
  <string name="satellite">Satellite</string>
  <string name="terrain">Terrain</string>
  <string name="next">Next</string>
  <string name="select_survey_title">Select a survey</string>
  <string name="survey_sync_hint">Once opened, surveys are available offline and synced automatically when online.</string>
  <string name="sync_dialog_subtitle">Your data will be synced shortly.</string>
  <string name="data_collected">Data collected</string>
  <string name="done">Done</string>
  <string name="skip">Skip</string>

  <string name="drop_pin">Drop pin</string>

  <string name="new_site">New data collection site</string>
  <string name="new_site_hint_text">Add new site and submit related data</string>
  <string name="drop_a_pin_tooltip_text">Drag your map until the center pin is on the desired location</string>
  <string name="current_location">Current location:</string>
  <string name="loading">Loading…</string>
  <string name="no_tasks_error">This job has no more tasks to complete</string>
  <string name="invalid_data_sharing_terms">This survey is misconfigured (no data sharing terms available). Please contact the survey organizer.</string>
  <string name="collect_data_viewer_error">Can’t collect data as user is a VIEWER</string>
  <string name="offline_map_imagery">Offline map imagery</string>
  <string name="offline_map_imagery_pref_description">Hide or show downloaded imagery</string>
  <string name="layers">Layers</string>
  <string name="base_map">Base map</string>
  <string name="offline_map_imagery_download_progress_dialog_message">Downloading offline map imagery…</string>
  <string name="multiple_regions">Multiple regions</string>
  <string name="permission_denied">Permission denied</string>
  <string name="close_app">Close app</string>
  <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
  <string name="save">Save</string>
  <string name="no_imagery_available_for_area">No imagery for this area. Select an area with imagery to download to your device.</string>
  <string name="selected_offline_area_size">The selected area may take up to %s\u00A0MB of space on your device</string>
  <string name="selected_offline_area_too_large">Zoom in and select a smaller area to download to your device</string>
  <string name="offline_area_size_loading_symbol">…</string>
  <string name="offline_area_select_cancel_button">Cancel</string>
  <string name="offline_area_selector_title">Download this area?</string>
  <string name="capture">Capture</string>
  <string name="surveys">Surveys</string>
  <string name="offline_icon_description">Icon shown when the survey is available offline</string>
  <string name="remove_offline_access">Remove offline access</string>
  <string name="point">Point</string>
  <string name="area">Area</string>
  <string name="unnamed_point">Unnamed point</string>
  <string name="unnamed_area">Unnamed area</string>
  <string name="offline_area_size_on_disk_mb">%s\u00A0MB on disk</string>
  <string name="offline_area_list_item_size_on_disk_mb">%s\u00A0MB</string>
  <string name="offline_downloaded_areas">Downloaded areas</string>
  <string name="offline_area_list_tip">Available for offline viewing</string>
  <string name="offline_area_list_item_icon">Offline area list item icon</string>
  <string name="no_surveys_available">No surveys available. Contact your survey organizer to get access.</string>
  <string name="previous">Previous</string>
  <string name="network_error_when_signing_in">Connect to the internet to sign in</string>
  <string name="camera_permissions_needed">You need to grant this application camera permissions to submit photos.</string>
  <string name="incomplete_area">Incomplete area</string>
  <string name="initializing">Initializing…</string>
  <string name="draw_area_task_instruction">Move the map and tap “Add point” to add points around the desired area.</string>
  <string name="close">Close</string>
  <string name="data_consent_dialog_title">Data collection agreement</string>
  <string name="map_location">Map location:</string>
  <string name="sign_out_dialog_title">Unsynced data</string>
  <string name="sign_out_dialog_body">If you sign out, any unsynced data will be discarded</string>
  <string name="suggest_data_collection_hint">Zoom in to start collecting data</string>
  <string name="read_only_data_collection_hint">Survey is read-only</string>
  <string name="predefined_data_collection_hint">Zoom in to a data collection site to collect data</string>
  <string name="no_submissions">No submissions</string>
  <string name="dismiss_info_popup">Dismiss</string>
  <string name="other">Other</string>
  <plurals name="submission_count">
    <item quantity="one">%d submission</item>
    <item quantity="other">%d submissions</item>
  </plurals>
  <string name="loi_name_dialog_title">Name this location</string>
  <string name="loi_name_dialog_body">A new data collection site will be created.</string>
  <string name="current_survey">Current survey</string>
  <string name="switch_survey">Switch survey</string>
  <string name="no_survey_selected">No survey selected</string>
  <string name="undo">Undo</string>
  <string name="view_licenses_title">Licenses</string>
  <string name="about">About</string>
  <string name="terms_of_service">Terms of service</string>
  <string name="about_ground">Ground is an open-source community project built by Google and FAO under the Forest Data Partnership with help from SIG, Ecam, and open-source community contributors. \n\nIt is licensed under the <annotation type="apache_license">Apache License, Version 2.0</annotation>. \n\nView other <annotation type="all_licenses">Licenses</annotation></string>
  <string name="failed">Failed</string>
  <string name="synced">Synced</string>
  <string name="syncing">Syncing</string>
  <string name="upload_pending">Upload pending</string>
  <string name="data_synced_media_pending">Data synced\n(media pending)</string>
  <string name="data_synced_media_pending_retry">Data synced\n(media pending retry)</string>
  <string name="media_syncing">Media syncing</string>
  <string name="data_sync_status">Data sync status</string>
  <string name="signout_warning">If you sign out, all unsaved data will be lost.</string>
  <string name="admin_request_access">To continue, contact your system administrator to request access.</string>
  <string name="signup_request_access">To continue, <annotation type="sign_up_link">sign up to request access</annotation>.</string>

  <!-- Settings -->
  <string name="general_title">General</string>
  <string name="upload_media_title">Upload Media</string>
  <string name="over_wifi_summary">Over Wi-Fi only</string>
  <string name="help_title">Help</string>
  <string name="visit_website_title">Visit website</string>
  <string name="send_feedback_title">Send feedback</string>
  <string name="report_summary">Report technical issues or suggest new locationsOfInterest</string>
  <string name="not_yet_impl_title">Not yet implemented</string>
  <string name="accuracy">Accuracy:</string>
  <!-- Data Sharing Consent Text -->
  <string name="data_sharing_no_terms">*No terms to display.*</string>
  <string name="data_sharing_private_message">
    ## Private data sharing
    \nData will only be shared with survey organizers, who may not share and use collected data publicly.
  </string>
  <string name="data_sharing_public_message">
    ## Public data sharing
    \nSurvey organizers may share and use data publicly under the *Creative Commons CC0 1.0 License*:
    \n# Creative Commons CC0 1.0 Universal
    \nCREATIVE COMMONS CORPORATION IS NOT A LAW FIRM AND DOES NOT PROVIDE LEGAL SERVICES. DISTRIBUTION OF THIS DOCUMENT DOES NOT CREATE AN ATTORNEY-CLIENT RELATIONSHIP. CREATIVE COMMONS PROVIDES THIS INFORMATION ON AN “AS-IS” BASIS. CREATIVE COMMONS MAKES NO WARRANTIES REGARDING THE USE OF THIS DOCUMENT OR THE INFORMATION OR WORKS PROVIDED HEREUNDER, AND DISCLAIMS LIABILITY FOR DAMAGES RESULTING FROM THE USE OF THIS DOCUMENT OR THE INFORMATION OR WORKS PROVIDED HEREUNDER.
    \n## Statement of Purpose
    \nThe laws of most jurisdictions throughout the world automatically confer exclusive Copyright and Related Rights (defined below) upon the creator and subsequent owner(s) (each and all, an “owner”) of an original work of authorship and/or a database (each, a “Work”).
    \nCertain owners wish to permanently relinquish those rights to a Work for the purpose of contributing to a commons of creative, cultural and scientific works (”Commons”) that the public can reliably and without fear of later claims of infringement build upon, modify, incorporate in other works, reuse and redistribute as freely as possible in any form whatsoever and for any purposes, including without limitation commercial purposes. These owners may contribute to the Commons to promote the ideal of a free culture and the further production of creative, cultural and scientific works, or to gain reputation or greater distribution for their Work in part through the use and efforts of others.
    \nFor these and/or other purposes and motivations, and without any expectation of additional consideration or compensation, the person associating CC0 with a Work (the “Affirmer”), to the extent that he or she is an owner of Copyright and Related Rights in the Work, voluntarily elects to apply CC0 to the Work and publicly distribute the Work under its terms, with knowledge of his or her Copyright and Related Rights in the Work and the meaning and intended legal effect of CC0 on those rights.
    \n1. **Copyright and Related Rights.** A Work made available under CC0 may be protected by copyright and related or neighboring rights (”Copyright and Related Rights”). Copyright and Related Rights include, but are not limited to, the following:
    \n    i. the right to reproduce, adapt, distribute, perform, display, communicate, and translate a Work;
    \n    ii. moral rights retained by the original author(s) and/or performer(s);
    \n    iii. publicity and privacy rights pertaining to a person’s image or likeness depicted in a Work;
    \n    iv. rights protecting against unfair competition in regards to a Work, subject to the limitations in paragraph 4(a), below;
    \n    v. rights protecting the extraction, dissemination, use and reuse of data in a Work;
    \n    vi. database rights (such as those arising under Directive 96/9/EC of the European Parliament and of the Council of 11 March 1996 on the legal protection of databases, and under any national implementation thereof, including any amended or successor version of such directive); and
    \n    vii. other similar, equivalent or corresponding rights throughout the world based on applicable law or treaty, and any national implementations thereof.
    \n2. **Waiver.** To the greatest extent permitted by, but not in contravention of, applicable law, Affirmer hereby overtly, fully, permanently, irrevocably and unconditionally waives, abandons, and surrenders all of Affirmer’s Copyright and Related Rights and associated claims and causes of action, whether now known or unknown (including existing as well as future claims and causes of action), in the Work (i) in all territories worldwide, (ii) for the maximum duration provided by applicable law or treaty (including future time extensions), (iii) in any current or future medium and for any number of copies, and (iv) for any purpose whatsoever, including without limitation commercial, advertising or promotional purposes (the “Waiver”). Affirmer makes the Waiver for the benefit of each member of the public at large and to the detriment of Affirmer’s heirs and successors, fully intending that such Waiver shall not be subject to revocation, rescission, cancellation, termination, or any other legal or equitable action to disrupt the quiet enjoyment of the Work by the public as contemplated by Affirmer’s express Statement of Purpose.
    \n3. **Public License Fallback.** Should any part of the Waiver for any reason be judged legally invalid or ineffective under applicable law, then the Waiver shall be preserved to the maximum extent permitted taking into account Affirmer’s express Statement of Purpose. In addition, to the extent the Waiver is so judged Affirmer hereby grants to each affected person a royalty-free, non transferable, non sublicensable, non exclusive, irrevocable and unconditional license to exercise Affirmer’s Copyright and Related Rights in the Work (i) in all territories worldwide, (ii) for the maximum duration provided by applicable law or treaty (including future time extensions), (iii) in any current or future medium and for any number of copies, and (iv) for any purpose whatsoever, including without limitation commercial, advertising or promotional purposes (the “License”). The License shall be deemed effective as of the date CC0 was applied by Affirmer to the Work. Should any part of the License for any reason be judged legally invalid or ineffective under applicable law, such partial invalidity or ineffectiveness shall not invalidate the remainder of the License, and in such case Affirmer hereby affirms that he or she will not (i) exercise any of his or her remaining Copyright and Related Rights in the Work or (ii) assert any associated claims and causes of action with respect to the Work, in either case contrary to Affirmer’s express Statement of Purpose.
    \n4. **Limitations and Disclaimers.**
    \n    a. No trademark or patent rights held by Affirmer are waived, abandoned, surrendered, licensed or otherwise affected by this document.
    \n    b. Affirmer offers the Work as-is and makes no representations or warranties of any kind concerning the Work, express, implied, statutory or otherwise, including without limitation warranties of title, merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, non infringement, or the absence of latent or other defects, accuracy, or the present or absence of errors, whether or not discoverable, all to the greatest extent permissible under applicable law.
    \n    c. Affirmer disclaims responsibility for clearing rights of other persons that may apply to the Work or any use thereof, including without limitation any person’s Copyright and Related Rights in the Work. Further, Affirmer disclaims responsibility for obtaining any necessary consents, permissions or other rights required for any use of the Work.
    \n    d. Affirmer understands and acknowledges that Creative Commons is not a party to this document and has no duty or obligation with respect to this CC0 or use of the Work.
  </string>
</resources>
